http://www.lightfair.com/privacy-policy

View Exhibitors
Explore the floor and see which manufacturers and exhibitors you can expect to find at LightFair 2021. Get ready to experience their latest products and solutions.
View Exhibitors
Pavilions
Discover the latest introductions in our Design, Exterior, Smart and New Exhibitor pavilions, and The Collective--an exclusive space for exhibitors who are IALD LIRC or IES Sustaining Members.
View Pavilions
Floor Plan
Show Floor Highlights
Pavilions
LightFair Innovation Awards
Conference
Conference
LightFair
Schedule
The LightFair Conference offers you more than 170 hours of accredited educational options – all developed to cover a broad spectrum of today’s most relevant topics.
View Schedule
Continuing Education Credits
Photo Gallery
Videos
Attend
Attend
Why Attend LightFair
Stay relevant. Stay ahead of the game. LightFair 2020 is packed with value for every minute you spend here.
Learn More
Registration is Now Open
Register for LightFair 2020. Join Lighting Design and Technology Leaders to Shape the Future of Our Industry.
Register Now
Pricing
LightFair Attendee Brochure
Exhibit
Exhibit
Exhibitor Prospectus
Discover why 500+ brands exhibit at LIGHTFAIR.
Learn More
Interested in Exhibiting?
Start your pre-qualification process to exhibit at LightFair today.
Learn More
Exhibitor Application
Pavilions
Sponsorship Opportunities
LightFair Innovation Awards
Press
Press
Press Releases
What’s happening at the latest LightFair.
Learn More
Exhibitor Press Releases
LightFair® Exhibitor’s News
Learn More
Press Assets
Press Registration
On-Site Media Center
Publications at LightFair
About
About
Management Committee
Three Partners. One Shared Goal. Meet the LightFair Management Committee.
Learn More
Frequently Asked Questions
LightFair® Exhibitor’s News
Learn More
Contact Us
Stay Connected
Privacy Policy
OverviewLIGHTFAIR INTERNATIONAL ("LFI", "we", "us" or "our") respects your privacy and is committed to complying with this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"), which describes what information we collect about you, how we collect it, how we use it, with whom we may share it and what choices you have regarding our use of your information. This Privacy Policy applies to your use of our website, located at https://www.lightfair.com, and any mobile applications associated with the website (collectively, the "Website") or any associated content, material, or functionality contained on the Website (the "Services" and, together with the Website, collectively, the "System"). This Privacy Policy also applies to information processed pursuant to our general business operations. You acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use and agree to be bound by such terms. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, references to "LFI" shall include LIGHTFAIR INTERNATIONAL and all of its respective members, affiliates, subsidiaries, directors, officers, agents, and employees.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is reflected by the effective date located at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. All such updates and amendments are effective immediately upon notice thereof, which we may give by any means, including, but not limited to, by posting a revised version of this Privacy Policy or other notice on the System. You should view this Privacy Policy often to stay informed of changes that may affect you. We expressly reserve the right to make any changes to this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice to you. Our electronically or otherwise properly stored copies of these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy shall be deemed to be the true, complete, valid, authentic, and enforceable copies of the version of the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy which were in force on each respective date you visited the System.
What Information Do We Collect
As described in detail below, we may collect certain identifying information from or about you (collectively, the "Collected Information"). Collected Information includes both Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. “Personal Information” means information that relates to or is reasonably capable of being associated with a specific individual. The categories of information that we collect include:
Identifiers. Example include your first and last name, address, and email address.
Educational and Professional Information. We collect educational information such as degrees earned, as well as, professional information such as company name.
Financial Account Information.
Account Information. To access certain areas of the System you must log in using a user ID and password. If you wish to use such areas of the System, you will be required to enter certain Personal Information (e.g., e-mail address, username or password) to gain access.
Web Browsing Information. We also collect information regarding how you interact with the System, which information may include pages you view, links you click or hover over, selections you make on the Websites, your web browser's HTTP referrer header, features you use, preferences you set, your web browser type and version, the operating system type and version of the device you are using to access the System, the Internet protocol (IP) address of the device you are using to access the System (or any portion thereof), general physical location, Internet service provider, in addition to any other information collected as further described in this Privacy Policy. Some of this information qualifies as (“Non-Personal Information”) rather than Personal Information.
Inferences drawn from other personal information. For example, information reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, or attitudes.
How Do We Collect It?
We may collect information about you in a number of ways and from a variety of sources. For example we may collect information when you:
(a) make inquiries about us, our products and services or contact us for any other reason so that we can process, deal with and respond to your queries or other issues including any complaints; or
(b) contact, register with, post to, like or follow any of our social media websites, pages, forums; or
(c) use or register on our System;
(d) subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or survey, enter or participate in any competitions or promotions; or
(e) from our business partners and affiliates.
In addition we may collect information through click tracking (in relation to your use of our Website and mobile application, including the content you access and any services you utilize) and through cookies (as further detailed below), tracking pixels and related technologies.
How Do We Use The Information That We Collect?
LFI may use the Personal Information we collect for various purposes, including (i) providing certain services to you; (ii) marketing activities; (iii) improving or personalizing the System's content, materials, and services; (iv) communicate with you regarding your order; and (v) more effectively and efficiently responding to both current and future user inquiries.
In addition to the uses mentioned or described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy or in the Terms of Use, we, our affiliates and subsidiaries, and our respective third party service providers may use the Collected Information to analyze and improve the content, features, Services, and Websites that we make available on the System, as well to conduct certain targeted marketing activities specific to users. We may send you information that you request from us, promotional materials regarding LFI's services and facilities, and any other communication for any other legitimate and lawful business purposes. Additionally, we may retain and use certain Collected Information to facilitate and otherwise address certain inquiries, requests, subscriptions, or business transactions and relationship with LFI or any of our affiliates, or respond to your questions or requests for information about or from LFI or any of our affiliates or trusted business partners. We may also use Collected Information as necessary to ensure compliance with any LFI policies and any applicable law.
LFI may use various analytics tools and technologies regarding how users interact with the various portions of the System that require storage of web session data. These tools and technologies are used to assist System users by using cookies and scripts (as described in the "Cookies and Usage Reports" section below) to collect and store information such as how users interact with the System, errors users encounter when using the System, device identifiers, how often users visit certain portions or components of the System, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to using to the System. Stored web session data used by such analytics services or tools is used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
With Whom Do We Share Information That We Collect?
In addition to the uses mentioned or described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy or in the Terms of Use, we may catalog and add Collected Information to our database.
We share, for our business purposes, all of the categories of information that we collect. We may share your information with our trusted vendor partners, such as payment processors, analytics providers, and our affiliates. We may also, from time to time, utilize a number of trusted business and marketing partners in delivering the content, materials, and opportunities available on or through the System.
We do not sell, rent, or lease our user lists or the identity of individual users to third parties. However, we may sell, use and disclose certain aggregated, anonymized information, to our affiliates, subsidiaries, or trusted business partners. Such information may also be shared with other users, LFI exhibitors or the general public for advertising, sales, informational, or comparison purposes. Such information is not Personal Information.
We may also disclose Collected Information if we become subject to a subpoena or court order, or if we are otherwise legally required to disclose information. We may also use and disclose Collected Information to establish or exercise our legal rights, to enforce the Terms of Use, to assert and defend against legal claims, or if we believe such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding actual or suspected illegal or fraudulent activities or potential threats to the physical safety or well-being of any person.
Cookies and Usage Reports
By placing a small file known as a "cookie" on your computer (or other device), LFI and its third party providers may passively gather information about your use of the System for several reasons, including, but not limited to, the following: statistics collection and analysis, System optimization, analytics (as described below), market research, and maintenance of user login information. For example, cookies on the Websites may track "macro" information, such as the number of independent visits made to the Websites each day, or "micro" information, such as individual users' IP addresses, downloads, and related traffic history (some of this information may be collected by web beacons, see below). The information that we and our third party providers track with cookies may include, but is not necessarily limited to, the type of browser (such as Google Chrome, Microsoft Edge or Internet Explorer) and Internet-connected device being used to access the System, your Internet protocol ("IP") address, your home domain or Internet service provider, your referrer URL (which is the URL for the website that you were viewing prior to visiting the System), how you were directed to the System, which specific pages you access on the System, how long you view each page, the time and date you access our System and the total number of visitors to the System and any portions thereof.
Most popular Internet browser applications will allow you to configure the browser so as not to accept cookies. However, setting your browser to reject cookies may, in certain instances, prevent you from taking full advantage of the System (or some portion thereof) and its capabilities, or cause some features of the System to function improperly or more slowly.
The System uses certain web analytics services provided by third parties in order to better understand your use of our Website (or other portions of the System) and how we can improve the System. Such analytics providers may collect information such as how often users visit the System, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other websites they used prior to coming to the System. We do not combine the information collected through the use of such analytics services with your Personal Information. Such third party analytics providers may utilize the data collected to track and examine use of the System, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with us.
As part of our suite of analytics, we also utilize web analysis services provided by Google. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Websites is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the System, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected on the System to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. To more fully understand how Google may use the data it collects on the System, please review "How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps", (located here or any successor URL).
Some of the areas of the System may also contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow LFI, and its third party providers or affiliates, to count and track users who have visited certain portions of the System and other similar traffic history. Web beacons collect only limited information, including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides.
How Can I Opt-Out of Promotional Correspondence?
Those individuals that express an interest in or consent to receiving communications from LFI, may receive email or other communications from us electronically. We consider, and you hereby acknowledge and agree, that providing your contact information on the System or otherwise evincing an interest constitutes valid consent to receive messages or other communications from LFI. However, if you would no longer like to receive emailed special offer information, notifications or other messages from us, please send an email to us at info@lightfair.com or click the link at the bottom of any email you receive from us and follow the instructions. Please allow us a reasonable period of time in order to satisfy your request, as some promotions may already be in progress. Please note that even if you opt-out as described above, LFI will retain your Collected Information for analytical purposes and other internal purposes including an ability to reconnect you with such Collected Information if you later opt-in to any of the data sharing, use or communications set forth above.
Change in Control and Other Organizational Changes
As LFI grows and develops its business, it is possible that its corporate structure or organization might change or that it might merge or otherwise combine with, or that it or portions of its business might be acquired by, another company. If LFI experiences a Change In Control (as defined below), then we may amend our privacy and information usage practices described in this Privacy Policy. Additionally, you should expect that Collected Information (including your Personal Information) would be one of the assets that will be transferred to the legal entity that succeeds our operation and ownership of the System. The privacy practices of the succeeding legal entity will then govern the Collected Information so transferred. However, if applicable law prohibits the succeeding legal entity's privacy policy from governing your Personal Information, then this Privacy Policy shall continue to govern. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Change In Control" means any of the following events: (i) a reorganization, merger, consolidation, acquisition or other restructuring involving all or substantially all of our voting securities and/or assets, by operation of law or otherwise; (ii) a general assignment for the benefit of creditors; (iii) appointment of a receiver for our business or assets; or (iv) our sale or liquidation, voluntarily or otherwise.
What Information Do We Collect for Sweepstakes, Promotions, Contests & Surveys?
You may wish to participate in online polls, surveys, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time. Participation in these polls, surveys, contests, sweepstakes and promotions is completely voluntary; you have a choice about whether or not to disclose information required to enter. Information requested may include personal contact information such as your name, address, date of birth, phone number, mobile phone number, e-mail address, username, and/or similar information. In addition, as noted above, we may share this information with our affiliates and other organizations or entities. In connection with any online polls, surveys, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time via the System, we use the information you provide to administer the polls, surveys, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions. Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we also may use the information to communicate with you, or the other people you select, about our services or our marketing partners may use such information to communicate with you about the online polls, surveys, contests, sweepstakes or other promotions or their products and services.
What Chioces Do You Have?
When submitting information, corresponding, making requests for information, and otherwise interacting with LFI and its representatives, you choose what information to supply or submit, whether you wish to receive further information, and how you may be contacted. Please take care to share only such information as is needed or that you believe is appropriate. Any promotional email we send to you will contain a link which will allow you to opt out of receiving any further correspondence. You may access and update information LFI has about you by emailing us at info@lightfair.com, calling us at (877) 437-4352 or logging into your account (if applicable).
For California Residents Only
This portion of our Privacy Policy advises California residents of rights provided in the California Consumer Privacy Act (the “CCPA”) and how California residents may exercise those rights. The CCPA currently exempts personal information reflecting a written or verbal business-to-business communication or transaction (“B2B Personal Information”) from certain of the law’s requirements, and also currently exempts personal information collected and used about a natural person acting as a business’s employee or contractor (“Personnel Information”). The rights described below may not apply to B2B Personal Information or Personnel Information.
If you are a California resident, you may request certain information from or certain action by us, such as exercising the access and deletion rights described below, or you may authorize an agent to make such a request on your behalf. We will seek to verify your identity and your agent’s authority when we receive an individual rights request from you or on your behalf to ensure the security of your Personal Information, and may need to collect additional Personal Information to do so.
Please direct any such rights requests (as further described below) or additional questions that you may have regarding this Privacy Policy to: info@lightfair.com; (877) 437-4352; or LIGHTFAIR INTERNATIONAL, 240 Peachtree Street, N.W. Suite 2200 Atlanta, GA 30303.
California residents have the right to request the deletion of Personal Information, but we may not delete some or all Personal Information, as required or permitted by applicable law, such as if the requested information is necessary to:
Complete your transaction;
Provide you a good or service;
Perform a contract between us and you;
Protect your security and prosecute those responsible for breaching it;
Fix our services in the case of a bug;
Protect the free speech rights of you or other users;
Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et seq.);
Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research;
Comply with a legal obligation; or
Make other internal and lawful uses of the information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.
If you are a California resident, you may also request to receive details about how we collect, use, and share your Personal Information. You may also request to receive the specific pieces of Personal Information that we have collected about you.
If a business sells Personal Information, you have a right to opt-out of that sale. We do not, and do not intend to, sell the Personal Information of California residents and, furthermore, do not have actual knowledge that we sell the Personal Information of consumers under 16 years old.
Businesses may not, and we do not, discriminate against you for exercising any CCPA rights, such as the access and deletion rights described above.
How Do We Protect Information Collected About You?
LFI implements commercially reasonable measures to secure and protect information. We use authorize.net to process payments. Nevertheless, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that information that you may transmit via the System or otherwise supply will be totally secure. You agree to immediately notify us of any breach of System's security, this Privacy Policy, or the Terms of Use of which you become aware.
Linked Websites
For your convenience, some hyperlinks may be posted on the System that link to other websites (the "Linked Websites"). Some Linked Websites are not under our control, such as facebook.com, twitter.com, and linkedin.com. We are not responsible for, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to, the privacy practices of any Linked Websites or of any companies that we do not own or control. Linked Websites may collect additional information to that which we collect on the System. Except for Linked Websites owned or operated by us, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any such Linked Websites, nor do we endorse any of these Linked Websites, the services or products described or offered on such Linked Websites, or any of the content contained on the Linked Websites. We encourage you to seek out and read the privacy policy of each website that you visit. In addition, should you happen to initiate a transaction on a Linked Website, even if you reached that Linked Website through the System, the information that you submit to complete that transaction becomes subject to the privacy practices of the operator of the applicable Linked Website. You should read each Linked Website's privacy policies to understand how Personal Information that is collected about you is used and protected.
California and Delaware "Do Not Track" Disclosures
California and Delaware law require LFI to indicate whether it honors "Do Not Track" settings in your browser concerning targeted advertising. LFI adheres to the standards set out in this Privacy Policy and does not monitor or follow any Do Not Track browser requests.
Visiting the System From Outside The United States
If you are visiting the System, or any part thereof, from outside of the United States of America, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using any portion of the System, you understand and consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities in the United States and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.
Children
The System is not intended for use or view by children under 13 years of age. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you must ask your parent or guardian to assist you in using the System. Furthermore, we may restrict entries to any contests, sweepstakes or promotions to entrants who are at least 18 years of age.
How to contact us
If you have any questions, comments or suggestions about the System, our services, LFI (or any of our affiliates), or our privacy practices, please contact us here info@lightfair.com or at the address below:
LIGHTFAIR INTERNATIONAL
240 Peachtree Street, N.W. Suite 2200 Atlanta, GA 30303
If you correspond with LFI through the System or via email, the Collected Information may include the content of, and metadata regarding, any correspondence you may have with us. We may share your messages with those within our organization who are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 03, 2020.
Las Vegas Convention CenterLas Vegas, NV USA
Trade ShowMay 5-7,
ConferenceMay 3-7,
Register
Become an Exhibitor
Conference schedule will be announced in January 2020.
Schedule
Pavilions
May 19, 2019
May 20, 2019
May 21, 2019
May 22, 2019
May 23, 2019
Design Pavilion
loading … please wait
Cookie Notice. We use cookies on this site to provide a great user experience. We gather information about how our site is used and provide personalized content. By clicking on the “I Understand.” button, you acknowledge that you have been notified of our use of cookies, and that you have read our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy. Thank You!
I Understand
Get the Latest Updates
